Guide to the School of Management, Yale University, Sound Recordings of Lectures and Presentations
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
School of Management, Yale University, sound recordings of lectures and presentations
1993-1999
RU 901
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.25
The materials consist of audiotapes documenting selected lectures and the "Conference on Foreign Direct Investment in Japan" at the Yale School of Management.
Yale University. School of Management
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 30-H (YRG 30-H), Audio-visual materials and memorabilia documenting the Yale School of Management.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site..
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologially.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of audiotapes documenting selected lectures and the "Conference on Foreign Direct Investment in Japan" at the Yale School of Management.
Forums (Discussion and debate); Lectures and lecturing; Meetings; Audiotapes; Yale University. School of Management
- Conference on Foreign Direct Investment in Japan proceedings, Accession 2002-A-138
  - 1993
    - Conference on Foreign Direct Investment in Japan, 1993 (Box 1)
      - 1993 May 14, 5
      - 1993 May 15, 2
    - SOM Dean's Distinguished Lecture Series (inaugural lecture)
      - Anita Roddick, founder and CEO of the Body Shop, Int'l. Topic: Socially responsible business, where profits meet principles, 1993 September 20; 1
  - 1996
    - 15 October, 1
  - 1997
    - LSA: Jeffrey Garten speaking on computer management problems, 1997 September 10; 1
  - 1999
    - Gary Hart at Luce Hall, 1999 December 2; 1
  - SOM 3/5, undated; 1